A Guide to the Governor Terry McAuliffe, Executive Office-Counselor's Office, Records, 2001-2006; 2008; 2010-2018 (bulk 2014-2017)
Library of Virginia
- V. Correspondence and Subject Files, 2002-2006; 2008; 2010-2017 (bulk 2014-2017)., Extent: 7.8 cubic feet (13 boxes). (Box 24-36)
  The 2010 Affordable Care Act (sometimes known as ACA or Obamacare) enabled states to expand their Medicaid program to cover all adults with income below 138% of the federal poverty level. Initially, the federal government fully paid for expansion; it now pays for 90%. The Virginia General Assembly and the Governor Robert McDonnell administration did not agree to expand Medicaid. Terry McAuliffe, during his successful 2013 gubernatorial campaign, promised to expand Medicaid. He was unsuccessful. The Medicaid records in this series document the McAuliffe's expansion attempts including: removing language from the 2014 state budget that appropriated extra Medicaid funds to a Medicaid commission but only if it approved expansion; and a 2016 line item veto of budget language that prevented the governor from expanding Medicaid without its permission. The General Assembly did not recognize McAuliffe's veto; they argued the governor could not veto conditions attached to an appropriate without vetoing the entire appropriation. The Virginia General Assembly approved Medicaid expansion as part of the FY2019-2020 state budget signed into law by Governor Ralph Northam on 7 June 2018.
  - Agency Documents, 2015-2016. (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Agency Services Impacted by a Potential Shutdown of State Government, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - ASPE Issue Brief, January 2014. (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Attorney General Official Opinions, 2013-2015. (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Attorney General, Equitable Sharing Agreement and Certification, 2012. (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Attorney General, Settlements (RESTRICTED), 2015; 2017. (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Avian Influenza, 2015. (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Bar Counsel Information, February 2014. (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Baseball, 2017. (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Camp Pendleton - State Military Reservation, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Campus Sexual Assault Task Force, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Candidate Campaign Committees, February 2014. (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), 2014-2015. (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), Tracy Retchin's Files, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Center for Innovative Technology (CIT), OAG Analysis, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - CGI Enterprise Applications Master Services Agreement, 2014. (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Citizens' Advisory Council (CAC)/Virginia Capitol Foundation (VCF), 2017. (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Commission to Ensure Integrity and Public Confidence in State Government, 2014-2015. (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Constituent Services - Miscellaneous, 2014; 2016. (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Continuation of Government Plans (no state budget), 2014. (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Council on Virginia's Future, 2015. (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Tevaris Crawford, 2017. (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Commonwealth v. Laura Fielder Crews (1 of 2), 2015. (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Commonwealth v. Laura Fielder Crews (2 of 2), 2015. (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Joseph J. Dick and Danial Williams (Norfolk Four), 2015. (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - District Courts of Virginia Clerk Staffing Levels, 2015. (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Dominion (SB 1349), 2015. (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Ethics, 2015. (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Ethics Commission, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Executive Order 55 (2012), Report of the Department for Aging and Rehabilitative Services (DARS), 2014. (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Fantasy Sports, undated. (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Federal Regulations, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Felon Disenfranchisement and Jury Duty, 2016. (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - First Lady Service Project, Childhood Nutrition, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Fort Monroe, 2011; 2013-2014. (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Fort Monroe, 2015. (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Fort Monroe, 2016. (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - General Correspondence, 2014. (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - General Correspondence, 2015. (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - General Correspondence, 2016. (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - General Correspondence and documents, 2017; undated. (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Gifts (Executive Order 2), 2014. (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Government Reform, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Governor-elect Terry McAuliffe Executive Leadership Workshop, 8 January 2014. (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Grant Information, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Leonard J. Hawkins-Parole Request, 2015. (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Hewlett Packard, 2015. (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Hurricane Preparedness, 2014. (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - Interstate Agreement on Detainers
    - Michelle Brown, #1472299, 2017. (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Darryl J. Early, #1446113, 2015. (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Eresto Kellum, #1576625, 2017. (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Maurice Turner, #1009480, 2015. (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - David K. Vanburen, #1277888, 2016. (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Clinton Vance, #1428916, 2016. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Joint Base Langley-Eustis, 2016. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Juveniles Sentenced to Life without Parole, undated. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Linwood Lambert, Jr., 2016. (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Files of Khaki LaRiviere, 2016-2017
    - Notebooks, 2016. (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Notebooks, 2016-2017. (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Notebooks, 2017; undated. (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Secretariat of Commerce and Trade, 2017 Session of the General Assembly (1 of 3), 2016-2017. (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - Secretariat of Commerce and Trade, 2017 Session of the General Assembly (2 of 3), 2016-2017. (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Secretariat of Commerce and Trade, 2017 Session of the General Assembly (3 of 3), 2016-2017. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Lautenberg Issues, 2010. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Legal Fellows/Interns
    - Virginia Veterans Services Demonstration Project, 2016. (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Summer Project Summary (Jade Moss), 2017. (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - William Morva Execution Research (Moss), 2017. (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - State Regulation Review (Moss), 2017. (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - William Pleasant Case (Moss), 2017. (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Constituent Response (Moss), 2017. (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Militia Laws of Virginia, 2017. (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Note pads (unidentified), undated. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Legislative Files
    - 2014 House of Delegates Bills reviewed by Carlos Hopkins (1 of 2). (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - 2014 House of Delegates Bills reviewed by Carlos Hopkins (2 of 2). (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - 2014 Senate Bills Reviewed by Carlos Hopkins. (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - 2016 General Assembly Notebook for Reconvened Session (Carlos Hopkins copy) (1 of 2). (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - 2016 General Assembly Notebook for Reconvened Session (Carlos Hopkins copy) (2 of 2). (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Lesbian, Gay, Bisexual, and Transgender (LGBT) Issues, 2015. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Letters, Outside Legal Services, 2014. (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Lethal Injection, 2013; undated. (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Library of Virginia, 2014; undated. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - Licensure of Abortion Facilities, 2014-2015. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Licensure of Abortion Facilities, 2016-2017. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Litigation
    - 2014
      - Notice of Class Action Settlement, Singleton, et al. v. First Student, Inc., et al (1 of 3), 2014. (Box 31, Folder 2)
      - Notice of Class Action Settlement, Singleton, et al. v. First Student, Inc., et al (2 of 3), 2014. (Box 31, Folder 3)
      - Notice of Class Action Settlement, Singleton, et al. v. First Student, Inc., et al (3 of 3), 2014. (Box 31, Folder 4)
      - Timothy B. Bostic, et al v. Janet M. Rainey, et al, 2014-2015. (Box 31, Folder 5)
      - David King, et al. v. Kathleen Sebelius, et al (1 of 2), 2014. (Box 31, Folder 6)
      - David King, et al. v. Kathleen Sebelius, et al (2 of 2), 2014. (Box 31, Folder 7)
      - Miscellaneous Litigation, 2014. (Box 31, Folder 8)
      - Petition for Assistance on Behalf of 19,000 Virginians in the Matter of Hyundai Mileage Litigation (1 of 2), 2014. (Box 31, Folder 9)
      - Petition for Assistance on Behalf of 19,000 Virginians in the Matter of Hyundai Mileage Litigation (2 of 2), 2014. (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - 2015
      - Banks v. GEICO (1 of 2), 2015-2016. (Box 31, Folder 11)
      - Banks v. GEICO (2 of 2), 2016-2017. (Box 31, Folder 12)
      - Barbara H. Lee et al v. Virginia State Board of Elections, et al, 2015-2016. (Box 31, Folder 13)
      - Miscellaneous Litigation (1 of 3), 2015. (Box 31, Folder 14)
      - Miscellaneous Litigation (2 of 3), 2015. (Box 31, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous Litigation (3 of 3), 2015. (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - 2016
      - Christopher L. Umberger v. Terry McAuliffe, Summons, 2016. (Box 31, Folder 17)
      - Felicia Hermann and Sandra Hermann v. Department of Medical Assistance, et al, 2016. (Box 31, Folder 18)
      - James E. Plowman v. Terence R. McAuliffe, 2016. (Box 31, Folder 19)
      - Jonathan R. Clark v. Virginia Department of State Police, 2016. (Box 31, Folder 20)
      - Carol Major v. Terence R. McAuliffe, 2016. (Box 31, Folder 21)
      - Troy Peterson #1691090 v. E.R. Barksdale, et al, 2016. (Box 31, Folder 22)
      - Washington Metropolitan Area Transit Authority (WMATA) False Claims Act Filing, 2016. (Box 31, Folder 23)
      - Sheri Daniel v. Timothy J. Sloan, CEO and President of Wells Fargo, 2016-2017. (Box 31, Folder 24)
      - Northrop Grumman Systems Corporation v. Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 2017. (Box 31, Folder 25)
      - Northrop Grumman Systems Corporation v. Virginia Information Technologies Agency, 2016. (Box 32, Folder 1)
      - William J. Howell, et al v. Terence R. McAuliffe, et al (1 of 2), 2016. (Box 32, Folder 2)
      - William J. Howell, et al v. Terence R. McAuliffe, et al (2 of 2), 2016. (Box 32, Folder 3)
      - William J. Howell, et al v. Terence R. McAuliffe, et al, Equal Protection Clause (EPC), 2016. (Box 32, Folder 4)
      - William J. Howell, et al v. Terence R. McAuliffe, et al, (Restoration of Rights Order), 2016. (Box 32, Folder 5)
      - William J. Howell, et al v. Terence R. McAuliffe, et al (Court Documents), 2016. (Box 32, Folder 6)
      - William J. Howell, et al v. Terence R. McAuliffe, et al (Clemency Research), 2016. (Box 32, Folder 7)
      - William J. Howell, et al v. Terence R. McAuliffe, et al (Clemency Research), 2016. (Box 32, Folder 8)
      - Miscellaneous Litigation, 2016. (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 2017
      - Tekiyah M. Yisrael v. Governor Timothy Kaine, et al, 2017. (Box 32, Folder 10)
      - Whitford v. Nichol, 2017. (Box 32, Folder 11)
      - Kevin Michael Jones v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 2017. (Box 32, Folder 12)
      - Tareq Aqel Mohammed Aziz, et al v. Donald Trump, et al, 2017. (Box 32, Folder 13)
      - Amador v. The Brickman Group, Ltd., LCC Settlement, 2017. (Box 32, Folder 14)
      - Mountain Valley Pipeline, LLC Docket No. CP16-10-000, 2017. (Box 32, Folder 15)
      - Miscellaneous Litigation, 2017. (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - Opinions
      - United States Supreme Court Decisions and Briefs, 2014. (Box 32, Folder 17)
      - United States Supreme Court Decisions and Briefs, 2014-2015. (Box 32, Folder 18)
      - United States Supreme Court Decisions and Briefs, 2015. (Box 32, Folder 19)
      - United States Supreme Court Decisions and Briefs, 2015. (Box 32, Folder 20)
      - United States Supreme Court Decisions, 2016. (Box 32, Folder 21)
      - Virginia Common Law Cases, 2014. (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Litigation - Redistricting Cases
    - Records (1 of 4), 2014-2015. (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - Records (2 of 4), 2014-2015. (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - Records (3 of 4), 2014-2015. (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - Records (4 of 4), 2014-2015. (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - VA 2021 Lawsuit, 2015. (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - Court Filings and Opinions, 2013-2015. (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - Court Filings and Opinions, 2015. (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence and Notes, 2015. (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Litigation - United States of America v. Robert F. McDonnell, et al
    - Baker and McKenzie, 2014. (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - Court Filings, 2014-2015. (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - Articles, 2014. (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - Governor McDonnell's State Pension, 2015. (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - Legal Bills, 2013. (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Douglas J. MacNeil-Correction of Writ of Mandamus, 2016. (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Marketing Mission, 2017. (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - McAuliffe Administration Accomplishment and Campaign Promises, 2017. (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Medicaid Expansion (1 of 6), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Medicaid Expansion (2 of 6), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Medicaid Expansion (3 of 6), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Medicaid Expansion (4 of 6), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Medicaid Expansion (5 of 6), 2014-2015. (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Medicaid Expansion (6 of 6), 2014-2015. (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Deputy Counselor Tracy Retchin (1 of 5), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Deputy Counselor Tracy Retchin (2 of 5), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Deputy Counselor Tracy Retchin (3 of 5), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Deputy Counselor Tracy Retchin (4 of 5), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Deputy Counselor Tracy Retchin (5 of 5), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Counselor Carlos Hopkins, (1 of 3), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Counselor Carlos Hopkins, (2 of 3), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Files of Counselor Carlos Hopkins, (3 of 3), 2014. (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Line Item Veto in Budget Bill Research (1 of 4), 2004; 2006; 2014. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Line Item Veto in Budget Bill Research (2 of 4), 2002; 2014. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Line Item Veto in Budget Bill Research (3 of 4), 2002-2004; 2008. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Line Item Veto in Budget Bill Research (4 of 4), 2002. (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Medicaid Expansion, Line Item Veto in Budget Bill, Attorney General Legal Advice (RESTRICTED), 2016. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Meeting Notes and Documents, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Meeting Notes, 2015-2017. (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Memorandum of Understanding between the Commonwealth of Virginia and Jeollanamdo Provincial Government of the Republic of Korea, 24 February 2016. (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Michael Morehart-OSIG Investigation (RESTRICTED), 2014. (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Mountain Valley Pipeline (MVP), 2016. (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - National Governors Association (NGA), 2014-2015. (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - North Anna Power Station License Application Decision, June 2017. (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Office of Civil Rights (OCR) Latasha Cotton v. Medical Learning Center, 2015. (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Office of Civil Rights (OCR) EBSFI v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Office of Civil Rights (OCR) EBSFI v. Commonwealth of Virginia, 2017. (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Office of Civil Rights (OCR) Title IX Investigation at the University of Virginia, 2015. (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Open Data Consultant Agreement, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Pamunkey Indian Tribe, 2016. (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Parole Abolition and Sentencing Reform, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Pelham "Confederate Memorial" Chapel Lease, 2015. (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Petersburg, 2016. (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Policy Office Meeting, 7 November 2016. (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Prison Rape Elimination Act (PREA), 2014-2015. (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Prisoner Re-Entry, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Privacy Act Release for Constituent Services, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Procurement, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - John M. Ragin-Writ of Certiorari, 2017. (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Reformulated Gasoline vs. Conventional (Riley Ingram), 2014. (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Refugees, 2017. (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Regulations, 2014-2015. (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Regulatory Boards in Virginia, 2015. (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Restoration of Rights, 2014. (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - RGGI (Regional Greenhouse Gas Initiative), 2015. (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Risk Management Plan, Suggested Amendment, undated. (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Same-Sex Marriage, Compliance Memos (Executive Order 30), 2014. (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Same-Sex Marriage, Virginia's Income Tax Treatment, 2014-2016. (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - SB 1197 (2015) - Hospitals Stillbirth Reporting, 2015. (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - SB 1393 (2015) - Compounding of Drugs for use in Executions, 2015. (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Program and Grant Agreement between Share our Strength, Inc. and the Office of the First Lady, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Small, Women-owned, and Minority-owned Business (SWAM), 2005; 2014-2015. (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Larry Smalls Writ of Habeas Corpus Ad Prosequendum, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - STARS Management Group, 17 May 2017. (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - State Budget Files, 2014-2015. (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - State Corporation Commission Approved Settlement with Insurance Companies, 2016-2017. (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Office of the State Inspector General, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Office of the State Inspector General, 2016. (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Super PACs, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Surety Bonds, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Surry-Skiffes Transmission Lines Mitigation Discussions, Nondisclosure Agreement, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Tax Exemptions, 2011; 2013. (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Trade Secrets, 2017. (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - TSA RIC Hub and Spoke Overview, undated. (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Uber Memorandum of Agreement, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Uniform Law Commission Meeting, July 2015. (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Unlicensed Locksmiths, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Unmanned Aircraft System (UAS) - Memorandum of Understanding (MOU), 2014. (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - VW Related - James Feinman, 2017. (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Rodrigo Vasquez-Lopez Petition, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Virginia Bar Association, Legislative Day for the 2016 Virginia General Assembly Session, 25 September 2015. (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Virginia Birth Injury Fund, 2016. (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Virginia Code Commission, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Virginia Code Commission, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Virginia Code Commission, 2016. (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Virginia Commission on Military Installations and Defense Activities, 2013; 2015. (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - Virginia Council on Women, 2016. (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Virginia Cyber Security Advisory Board, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Virginia Cyber Security Commission, First Report, August 2015. (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Virginia Department of Aviation, New Jet, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Virginia Department of Corrections, 2016-2017. (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Virginia Department of Corrections, Pardon and Parole Information, FY 2012-2016. (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Virginia Department of Emergency Management, 2014; 2017. (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Virginia Department of Forensic Science, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Virginia Department of General Services, Reports, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Virginia Department of Health, Regulatory Actions Under Review in Governor's Office, May 2015. (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Virginia Department of Human Resource Management Circulation of ACA Guidance, 2016. (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Virginia Department of the Treasury, Risk Management Plan, 2016. (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Virginia Department of Transportation, 2014-2015. (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - Virginia Department of Veterans Services, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Virginia Growth and Opportunity Act, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - Virginia Horse Center, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Virginia Office of Intergovernmental Affairs, 2014. (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Virginia Public-Private Partnerships, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Virginia State Board of Elections, 2014-2015. (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Virginia Uranium, Inc., 2015. (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Virginia Veteran and Family Support (VVFS) Workgroup, 2015-2016. (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Robert West, 2016. (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Worker Misclassification, 2017. (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Workforce Development, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Workforce Transition Act, 2015. (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Virginia Alcoholic Beverage Control, Martese Rashaad Johnson Case (RESTRICTED)
    - FOIA request for Email, March-April 2015. (Box 36, Folder 1)
    - Virginia State Police Investigation Concerning Martese Rashaad Johnson, 8 July 2015. (Box 36, Folder 2)
    - Virginia State Police Report (1 of 2), 10 July 2015. (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Virginia State Police Report (2 of 2), 10 July 2015. (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Fact Finding Investigation (copy 1), 31 July 2015. (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Fact Finding Investigation (copy 2), 31 July 2015. (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - Fact Finding Investigation (copy 3), 31 July 2015. (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Withholding a Personnel Record, 18 August 2015. (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Martese Johnson v. Virginia Department of Alcoholic Beverage, et al, 13 October 2015. (Box 36, Folder 9)